Summary:
In summary,
there are a few specific rinses
that will help prevent mucositis.
Baking Soda and MuGuard.
Please do these as instructed
from the start of radiation.
The better you adhere to this,
the more you will be rewarded
later into the treatment.
It is important to do this step
even if you are not experiencing
mucositis or pain.
If the mucositis worsens,
we may add numbing medications, lidocaine
or pain relieving medication.
Doxepin or Morphine
to help you through it.
It is important that you follow closely
how to use them.
Please feel free to watch
and rewatch the videos
to make sure they are clear to you
before using.
And feel free to ask our team
any questions to help clarify.
Thank you for watching.